redalkemi.com 2007-12-12

# RedAlkemi : Privacy Policy : Trademarks & Copyrights Redalkemi : Terms amd services

Privacy Policy

**Home** » Privacy Policy

At RedAlkemi we take your privacy issues very seriously. The following points are the measures we abide by, to provide our users with a safe online environment. These rules govern the use of the website RedAlkemi.com. The rules set forth herein apply to all materials, online communications and other information that is or becomes available on RedAlkemi.com.

In short, we do not disclose, share or sell our site users data or our client data to any outside or third parties. When our clients enlist our services we request certain details to ensure we provide them with the best possible services to suit their unique business model.

We expect our users to adhere to our policies, if our users do not agree with these policies we ask them to refrain from using this site. At all times we reserve the right to modify and alter our site and our privacy policy as we see fit. It is the responsibility of the user to make regular checks on our policies to ensure they are operating in accordance with our terms. The continued use of RedAlkemi.com following any changes to these terms shall indicate, that as a user, you have accepted those changes.

We generally require some basic personal information from our clients including their name, business and trading name, email address and contact details. Depending on the services requested, we shall be seeking varying degree of business data. The data we collect is used to build a thorough profile of our clients, complete with business goals and ambitions. We may ask you to supply us with previous marketing, advertising or promotion strategies employed by your company, particularly online and search engine optimization programs.

All the information collected will be treated in the utmost confidence. Only trusted members of the RedAlkemi family will have access to client information on a need-to-know basis. Any correspondence, presentations or data that need to be send to our clients will be delivered through secure online programs that require password authentication. RedAlkemi will only disclose client information to authorized entities if directed by a competent court of law or a legal body. Such requests would be entertained in accordance with international privacy laws.

Our site enforces strict security measures and programs to ensure the online security of all our visitors and clients. These measures are initiated to prevent stored data and information being accessed by fraudulent users.

As is prevalent on many websites, RedAlkemi may use cookies to track and monitor visitors to our website in order to serve most relevant content so as to improve user experience on our website. The information we collect through these cookies is solely for use at RedAlkemi. We may elect to record Domain Names, IP Numbers, Browser and Platform types, Referral information along with time, date and duration of visits. This helps us build a stronger profile of the clients and visitors to our site, allowing us to cater for and develop services for their benefit. Cookies can be removed from computers if so desired by the user, please consult the help function in your browser for related assistance. We do not record or collect email addresses through cookies, we only correspond with emails that have been supplied to us by our users and clients.

All users and visitors to our website should be aware that we are not responsible for the control, security or materials featured on external links from our site. Similarly, links to our website may be created without our prior consent or knowledge and we therefore can not provide any assurances for these links. RedAlkemi can not be held responsible for any direct or indirect harm, offense, loss or damage experienced through linked web sites. We are not responsible for the content or material provided on outside web sites, the opinions expressed and accuracy of the content does not reflect the views of RedAlkemi.

Our users must agree not to reproduce, change or sell any of the images or content present on our website, without seeking prior written consent from RedAlkemi. Trademarks or logos of other companies may appear on our website. Such trademarks and logos are not the property of RedAlkemi but are owned by their respective companies. If you feel that there is a violation of use of any such trademarks or logos, please bring it to our attention at: 

The content and services on RedAlkemi.com is provided on an "as is" basis without warranties of any kind, either expressed or implied, as to the operation of this site. This includes without limitation, the information, content, materials and products included on this site. RedAlkemi are not aware of any infringement of copyrighted images, content or trademarks on this site and all efforts are observed to ensure no copyrighted materials are used on this site. We do not warrant that any information is complete, accurate or fit for any particular use or that it will continue to be available uninterrupted or error free or that any information is free of rogue programming. RedAlkemi.com's liability is limited to the fullest extent permitted by law.

By using this site, tools and information, the user is expressing a complete understanding and acceptance of the terms listed in this Privacy & Disclaimer Policy. If you have any questions or concerns, please email us at:
